=The Cruel Tribunal=
=Episode 22=
Things have come to this.
There is no turning back for me.
One day,
when my soul returns,
we will be a family reunited again.
The traitor Songpiao
rebelled using the name of Lu Cen,
(Arrest Warrant)
murdered loyal ministers,
and plotted to form
a faction to usurp the throne.
This is treacherous
(Arrest Warrant)
and heinous.
(Arrest Traitor Songpiao)
- Xiaobai.
- Ordered for nationwide arrest.
- Xiaobai!
- Anyone who captures him
or provides clues...
Xiaobai.
What are you doing?
They will be rewarded.
Where is Xiaobai?
Miss Xiaobai isn't here.
Anyone who dares to hide or harbor him
will share the same crime,
- Where is she?
- with their head being hung at Wumen.
Miss Xiaobai left the legal house
and said she wouldn't come back.
Did she say where she was going?
She went to the pier.
What are you doing?
Are you still not clear about it?
Only by killing you
can I succeed to the throne.
Then let me tell you,
I have severed ties with Mother.
I demoted myself to a commoner
and am no longer a prince.
I have had no interest
in the throne since I was young.
Now,
I only want to find
Jiang Xiaobai as soon as possible
and fly away with her.
Get out of the way!
They are all Jingshu's people.
We are nothing more than
pawns of Jingshu.
We have fallen into a trap.
Be careful!
Go.
I only now know
it was my mother
who killed your mother.
I know apologizing now
cannot make up for anything.
I am not begging for
your forgiveness for her either.
No.
But I
must say...
Songpiao,
I'm sorry.
No,
these things
have nothing to do with you.
I was wrong.
I misunderstood you.
Go.
I must take you away.
Take this.
Find...
Find Jiang Xiaobai for me.
Tell her
to live well.
No.
If you want to go,
go by yourself.
Let's go.
I will take you to find her.
Go!
If you don't leave now,
we will die here.
Sizhou.
Sizhou!
Your Highness,
the men sent out just now reported
that they have brought back
the First Prince's body.
It didn't attract anyone's attention.
But
the Second Prince escaped.
Tidy up Zhou's remains carefully.
I don't want to see any stains on him.
Yes, Your Highness.
(Jingshu,)
(if I look back,)
(all of this)
(will be over.)
♪The candle burns down
to its final glow♪
♪Cold fragrance clings to my hem♪
♪You gently smooth my hair♪
♪Yet your gaze drifts far away♪
♪A hidden blade lies beneath your smile♪
♪You turn away
as if nothing has changed♪
♪Step by step, I walk away♪
♪Each step breaks my heart anew♪
♪If fate had not gone astray♪
♪Why leave me
standing alone in the wind?♪
♪We shared one fleeting life together♪
♪Yet all that's left
is warmth upon my fingertips♪
♪I'd melt this night into ink♪
♪And write of every meeting
and every parting♪
♪If next life asks
about the days gone by♪
♪I'll only say that once♪
♪I called your name♪
♪The silent stars hang low♪
♪The river keeps flowing east♪
♪I linger in the old tower♪
♪Waiting for you,
though all is now empty♪
♪This life still owes us a bow♪
♪May the next repay us with a dream♪
♪Beyond here lie
endless mountains and rivers♪
♪I dare not turn for one last look♪
♪If fate had not gone astray♪
♪Why bury this heart beneath the frost?♪
♪We shared one fleeting life together♪
♪Now only fading warmth
remains in my palm♪
♪I'd melt this night into ink♪
♪And paint a winter between your brows♪
♪If we meet again in another life♪
♪Will you believe that tonight♪
♪Was when we first met?♪
♪Was when we met for the last time?♪